Sisi Vieira

Full Stack Developer

I'm a full-stack software developer with experience developing solutions for clients in the healthcare industry. I take pride in my time-management skills, as well as my ability to stay focused and motivated while facing new challenges. I enjoy problem-solving while working individually or within teams. I look forward to learning new skills and building strong, lasting relationships.

EXPERIENCE

I-ology, Remote — Full-Stack Development Intern

Mar 2022- May 2022

At I-ology, I was responsible for developing projects, from concept to completion, for clients in the healthcare industry. I had strong input in the design and architecture of each feature. I developed processes that integrated with third-party vendors to manage patient data and schedule appointments. Additionally, I was responsible for the development of front-end components that allowed the user to integrate with back-end processes allowing them to log in and out, and manage their profile, insurance information, and appointment details.

Spring Market, Portland, OR — *Information Clerk*

2015 - 2022

At Spring Market, I was the first point of contact for clients looking to place orders, or collect product information. While managing client requests, I was also responsible for working with members of my team to ensure the successful delivery of each order. Through my solid communication and multi-tasking skills, I had a direct impact on increasing client sales by 10% each year.

EDUCATION

Epicodus — Full-Stack Software Engineering Program

2021 - 2022

At Epicodus, I completed a 10-month-long intensive learning program focused on full-stack software engineering. During my time at Epicodus, I developed over 60 projects using C# and .NET Core, JavaScript, React, and CSS. I worked individually and within teams to design and implement each project. It was through Epicodus that I learned to handle multiple requirements simultaneously and receive new instructions on the fly.

Portland State University, Portland, OR — *Communication/General*

2011 - 2015

(503) 419-8085 cicy886@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/sisi-vieira github.com/cicy886

SKILLS

HTML/ CSS/ Sass
Node.js/ JavaScript/ jQuery
React/ Redux/ Vue
C#/ .NET Core
MySQL/ NoSQL/ Firebase
Umbraco Cloud CMS
API Development
Object-Oriented Programming
Test-Driven Development
Jira/ Kanban/ Agile development
methodology

PROJECTS

Local Business API C#, .NET Core, MySQL

The Local Business API is a tool that allows users to search for businesses in their area. Users can filter their search by category or cost-of-service. This API was designed to integrate with any front-end implementation. Check out the source code here - https://github.com/cicy886/Local-businessApi.Solution

Tarot Card Reader Node.Js, React

Tarot Card Reader is an app that simulates the experience of receiving a tarot card reading. Find out what the future holds for your love life, health, and career. In addition, this project serves as an educational tool allowing users to learn the meanings behind all 78 tarot cards. Visit the site here -

https://cicy886.github.io/tarot-card-reader/#/